Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
I just dropped by, this is it.
It's started.
Yay.
The morning chimes have sounded.
We are the new art directors.
Yes, so the show has started early,
Before we start, I would like to decide who will be the MC for today's show.
Quickly.
There are 1 and 2 tags here,
So, let's choose one or two.
We will choose one, and then you can choose one of the 12 you like.
Huh?
Ahh!
Okay, we'll go with the one on the left, or the one on the right, or the one on the left, or the one on the right, or the one on the left, or the one on the right.
Starter.
It's been a while since we've seen each other.
It's been a while since we've seen each other... and it's been a while since we've seen each other.
I wonder if there's ever been three of us... but there's definitely been... a rare combination.
But if there were 10 of us...
It's rare. They don't come around that often.
We're called the “Yasuragi duo.” We're Toragi and Noragi Sakuragi.
I wonder if everyone has voted... if we can close the voting.
I was going to count down the votes.
I'm sorry. Please do it.
And now, the MC for today is number two.
Today's MC is Mr. Raggi.
I'm Cocona Sakuragi, and I'll be your MC for today.
And now, let's get started with today's showroom, the delightful and unfortunate Ebichu showroom.
Today is the 69th Ebichu's Delightful and Marital Showroom.
Ebichu's New Internation
Thank you very much for watching Ebitu's Delightful and Married Couple Showroom.
Thank you very much.
Ebichu's Delightful and Married Couple Showroom is our sister showroom!
It's the sister show of Uka's showroom!
So, it's time to spread the word! So, it's spread time here.
Yay time!
In order to get as many people as possible to watch this distribution, I'm going to do my mouth on Ebichu's official X page now,
I'm going to do a mouthful of mouthfuls.
I'm going to be a trumpet.
I'm going to be a trumpet. All of it.
That's right. I'll do my mouth, so please spread the word, everyone.
So, Muraizawa-san, can we have a picture, please?
Yes. What shall I do? Then, I'll take this one?
Thank you very much.
So please spread the word!
So today, I'd like to try a project like this.
It's called the “Delightful Married Couple Questionnaire.
Wait a minute, I forgot to bring the questionnaire.
I forgot it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What? Okay, I'll explain.
Before a talk, we take a questionnaire to decide what to talk about.
That's the questionnaire talk, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Wait a minute.
I'll take the questionnaire.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
You went to get it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry again. I completely forgot.
Let's start with the theme of the talk.
Let's start with the theme.
Let's see... (1) 15th Anniversary Tour: Miyagi, Fukuoka, Niigata and Kanagawa
(1) 15th anniversary tour in Miyagi, Fukuoka, Niigata and Kanagawa (2) Information gathering in Taipei (3) Photo book release for the members in their senior year (4) Gags to use when things get awkward
(5) Korean words used by young people (6) I don't understand the picture at all (7) I'm going to attend a very hot concert
(8) Participating in a very hot live concert (8) Wu-Tang village
ijo's voice Naka nonsense
I see what you mean about the kitchen car. I see.
So, I would like to ask you to vote for the one you are most interested in, and then I would like to talk about the one that comes in first. So, I would like to ask you all to vote for the one you are most interested in, and then we will talk about the one that came in first among them.
Yes, by all means. You're pretty obvious with your handwriting.
Is it obvious? Yes, I can tell by the words. I just saw the comments.
Really? Yes, I'm sure.
What do you think it will be? Many people are curious about Utamura. Indeed, Utamura.
What do you think? You are voting now, right? Voting is underway. Voting is open.
What's the number? It's going on and on and on and on. Aya said it's easy to understand because of your rounded handwriting. You're right, it's hard to tell.
Maybe we're writing in different ways to camouflage each other. It's true, but it's also true that Aya-chan is a big fan of Korean words used by young people.
It's clear even in the content. It's very clear.
I want to know the gag too. I'm curious about gags. Gags are dangerous, aren't they? It's a little scary. I'd like to know a lot more, though.
So, shall we close the voting? I would like to close it. Voting is closed.
De-da-da-da-da-da-da.
The sound of the deadline is “De-De-De-De-De-De”. It is a unique sound.
Okay, now the voting results.
The result is No. 1? The 15th anniversary tour.
Miyagi, Fukuoka, Niigata, Kanagawa
Yay!
You all know what you're talking about, don't you?
Yes, we are in the middle of the tour. We are on tour now.
That's right.
I think it's the most important thing.
That's true. That's right. We are on our 15th anniversary tour.
We are currently on a tour called “The Other Side of Indigo Hour,
Yes, we are.
We are currently touring in these four places?
The fifth show?
This will be the fifth show.
Have you been to a few more? I have already been to one more. The other night at Kaltz Kawasaki.
Omiya is missing?
We've probably done five shows, and the next one will be the sixth. That's right. There were performances in Ichikawa and Omiya, too.
Do you have any places that remain in your memory?
Any particular place? Places?
The word chance was a little strange.
Land. Land is a place.
Well, I wonder where. But I was nervous on the first day.
I was the most nervous on the first day.
Everyone was nervous at the beginning. Everyone was nervous, right at the beginning.
We were nervous.
That was the key to this tour, or rather, the beginning,
Everyone was probably wondering how they should look at it,
So I had to make a clear decision,
I remember being extremely nervous.
That's right.
That part.
That's for sure.
The first song.
But, you know, when we performed it for the first time, everyone's call.
Oh, sure.
I thought the level of excitement was very encouraging. That's for sure. Everyone was amazing. You know, it's not so easy...you know, that first song, I'm trying to keep my voice down.
But, oh, you've already said it. It was like they were saying it, but it was a little difficult to call, and they were practicing a little too much.
Even though it was a song call, everyone was amazing. They used it perfectly.
It was a lot of fun.
Moreover, after the first or second performance, the audience began to understand the point of excitement, so some parts of the performance were changed or added accordingly.
The momentum of the audience was so great that we brushed up the points to make the show even more exciting.
It's true.
It feels like we are making something together. It's a lot of fun.
Yes, it is.
Do you have that? Aya. I have fond memories.
The one that remains in your memory is the encore performance of “Eat the Medama” at Kawasaki, right?
Well, yes.
The one before.
I think it was in Niigata.
Niigata? That's right. The setlist that day in Niigata had songs that hadn't been played in a while.
I heard that adults didn't buy it because there were many songs that hadn't been played in a long time in the daily setlist.
Oh, that's right.
The set was a bit aggressive, and when they played the big highlight, when the intro came on, it was like a big rush of excitement.
I was surprised.
I was so surprised, and everyone cheered louder than I had expected.
I was also a bit excited.
That's for sure. And the eyeballs from the adults were both welling up, weren't they? Both of them and the introduction.
It was amazing.
The encores changed each day, so I could hear fresh reactions every time.
That's for sure. Indeed.
I'm ready for one more encore. It gets me fired up and ready to go even harder.
It makes you feel passionate, doesn't it?
That's for sure. When they performed “EBISOLI,” it was amazing. Why do people like Ebizori so much?
I don't know, maybe it's because it was their debut indie song, or maybe it's that squeaky sound that makes them all sick.
Maybe they already have that disease. The sound of the engine. When I hear “squeak,” I get a “woof” feeling.
That's why I'm a little worried.
It's funny, because they get excited with that kind of energy.
It's the first encore every time we play.
If you haven't come yet, I'd love it if you'd come out and see us.
If you haven't come yet, I'd love it if you could come and see us at the next show on June 1st.
We're looking forward to seeing you.
We'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you.
So let's do one more thing.
That's right.
Do we have to decide one more time?
One more time.
We're going to take a survey, so please choose the one you like.
Please choose one.
nehme
I hope you eat a lot of delicious food in Hokkaido!
I'd like to try some seafood, right?
There's no such thing as good food that only the locals know about, so you'll have to ask around.
If I've been going back every year, you know...
I'd like to meet something new. Sapporo, right?
I wonder if there's anything there.
What do you want? horses... seafood... oysters... oysters...
Oysters in Hokkaido are more basic than those in Kyushu, but they're rich.
I'm sure you'll like the sight of them.
I'm going to close up now.
What happened to the bike?
I wonder what happened to number 4.
I'm not in the mood...
It's not at all surprising...
I was out to dinner with friends and we split the bill, and I suddenly remembered that I'd thought of something good and grinned... I'm going out to eat with my friends and we're splitting the bill, and I suddenly remembered that I'd thought of a good gag to use in awkward situations.
I'm going to pay for it today, and I'm going to pay for it.
At times like that, I'm like, “Okay, I'll pay today, but I'll pay next time.
When we were talking about paying today but paying next time, she said, “Pay me, then I'll pay you.
And then when the girl who decided to pay went to the cash register, she didn't have enough change for a wave of change.
I don't know, I guess it's like that, you know... you know... you're embarrassed or something.
And then there are those times when you say you'll pay, but the fact that you don't have the change makes things a little awkward, you know?
I'll pay you tomorrow.” In that awkward moment, there was a funny gag.
You lick the bill as if you're going to take it, and then you say, “I'll pay this.
No, that's the kind of thing you do when you pay a bill.
You know, before you stick your hand in the cozenille, you do a little “lick”.
I see... I see... Don't you think we can all use this?
Yes, it's true, but it's very detailed.
It's really detailed.
It's a very specific situation. It can't be used anytime.
I really want everyone to use it in those core awkward and embarrassing situations when splitting a bill.
I'm sure, but I might just accept it.
Don't go into it. It's like, “This is how this girl does it.
That much? That much? So much? I don't know. I think I would have told you if I felt like I could really get into it.
What is it? I see.
If it's the first time you've had dinner or the second time you've had dinner...
Oh, man, now the comments are adding to the awkwardness.
I feel like it's getting more awkward.
I thought about it, but I couldn't use them because I thought they were dangerous chopsticks.
Well, I thought we could talk about it in the showroom, and if it sounded good, we could use them.
I thought we'd talk about it in the showroom, and if it sounded good, we'd use them, but...
I was thinking of using it if it sounds good, but I don't think we should use it.
It's a gag that can be used in such situations.
It's true, when there's a great kid who can make fun of anything.
I'll try my best.
Next time I'm in a situation like that, I'll just say, “That's a good one.
I'll say it.
When my sister and Aya go out for dinner, if you do that...
Aya's finger pens when she gives coins.
It's like... It's like... It's a little bit old man like...
It's like a double whammy.
I think she's going to get hurt herself.
I'll be careful not to do that.I'll be careful not to do this one.
Well, it's interesting, that's for sure, that's for sure.
Thank you very much.
He doesn't even lick the change.
That's true. Kids nowadays don't lick it like this.
I don't think so... you're right... when they open a plastic bag like this, they lick it off their mothers, don't you remember?
I see... the kid's mom is young.
That's why they lick them like this.
I grew up watching them do it.
I see.
You've come up with something.
That's old.
Well, if you know what I mean.
People who know.
Yeah, I do.
Thank you all very much.
I see.
So, Shirai, who asked for Kyoto...
It was... now...
I'll get myself together.
Get yourself together.
Take it easy.
Next subject, will you choose one?
Yes, sir.
Anything other than #1 and #4, please, and don't give me #4 ever again. I want to hear more.
If you have any more, please let's decide whether or not to adopt them.
You're right, you're right.
Is there anyone who's pulling the gag one more time?
No more gags... no more gags.
No more “it's a problem.” Why not?
Why not?
I don't know.
Yes.
And...
De-da-da-da-da.
What do you think? How about.
Number 8.
Oh!
Wu-Tang Village!
Yay! Thank you very much.
I wanted to talk to you.
Yes, I think Wu-Tang Village is Familien, and this year too, Familien in summer.
I have 4 and 8 the same.
Wait, stop it, guys.
Why are you giving us the same percentage?
Then I would have preferred number 4 by far.
What's wrong with that? You're being too subtle.
Of course I'm going to choose Wu-Tang.
Yes, let's go with Wu-Tang.
Oh, no, I'm surprised you noticed that.
You scared me.
We're serving the same thing.
That was a mistake.
Let's make it Wu-Tang Village.
Wu-Tang Village, please.
We have a family, and we are going to have the Wu-Tang Village, also known as Wu-Tang Village Kitchen Car again this year,
We'll be there just in time,
We have to decide what we are going to serve in Wu-Tang Village by this week.
So we'd like to have a consultation here to get everyone's opinion.
I'd like to have a consultation meeting with everyone's opinions, and I'd really appreciate it if you could help me out.
UtamuraYes, I said last time that I wanted to bring insects to the concert, but I don't think so.
I said I wanted to make a bug come out, but I don't think I'll do it.
I'm sure you've already been rejected by everyone, so I'm afraid it won't happen this time.
I'm sorry to say that I don't think it's going to happen this time.
So, the beef is delicious... and it's in the 88 nests of insects... the eight nests are on top of honey...
I'm sure you're right... the love ones are pretty good...
Nesmento's are becoming mainstream, and they're delicious, but the ones that aren't Squeeze's are a little...
There's a kind of chrysalis that's fed to crunchy foods, and it tastes like a jellyfish.
I'm sure it tastes more like jagariko than rikko.
I recommend it.
What would you like to eat?
I don't want to eat anything! I'm too scared!It's too scary.
I saw a show once where they made a plan to eat white ant jelly.
Yeah, that's a lie.
It was a penalty game.
Yeah, it was a punishment.
Is that a reward?
Not really a reward.
You don't usually eat. I want to eat something like that. I want something that tastes fresh.
I see. You are an adventurer. I see. I want everyone to have that kind of adventure.
I see. You mean you wanted to show it to them?
That's right. I wanted to open new doors.
I see. I'm not so sure about the insects.
What would you like? I just glanced at it.
I saw your comment about shallow balls and thought they might be good, and the members were into them for a while, and I'm still into them now, up to four.
So, girls would come, and it would be cold, and it would be delicious, and it would be like Hawaiian inside.
I'm sure it's a new thing, but it's certainly a lunch box, or a bowl of rice.
It's not so easy to get a member out.
It's good, it's good.
It's good.
Poke-don.
What do you think? Açai.
I can't get bugs in my acai.
Acai with white ants.
Garlic shrimp?
Yeah!
Together.
That sounds so good.
Garlic shrimp and acai bowl.
Aya would look good with that. They serve that kind of thing.
Do I look good?
Yes, I do.
I don't know if I'd look good with that. From the kitchen.
Do you think it looks good?
Overseas.
Isn't she a fashionable type? Overseas, yes, for sure. It's like coming to Lake Yamanaka and feeling like you're at a resort.
You can almost feel it. A Hawaiian kitchen is possible.
Very possible. I like the kalekshake. There is so much. I like the kalekshake.
What do you think? I think I've already decided on this one. I think it's really good. I think it's really good right now.
Acai is good. Acai what? What do you put in it?
I usually have acai, banana, kiwi, blueberries, and some flakes.
Almonds?
Nuts?
Oh, nuts. Mixed nuts.
Mixed nuts with honey.
Honey is a must. Honey is a must. It's delicious. Don't some stores put chocolate chips in it? Sounds delicious.
That sounds delicious. I've never had it yet, but I heard that a very popular restaurant with a long line of customers has an additional menu item called “chocolate chip”.
Sounds delicious. I'm going to try that too. It's really good.
And there's Hawaiian food. There's Hawaiian. What would you put next to it?
What would be good?
Oh my God, is there a lot of “bahn mi” going on here? Maybe. What is a “Bain Mee”? I don't know what a “bahn mi” is. I don't know. I just saw it.
Oh, I get it. It's a Vietnamese sandwich. I don't know.
I don't know what to call it. Is it like a burrito? Or is it more like a...? It's on some kind of hot dog-like bread,
It's like a burrito, but with vegetables.
It's kind of like a burrito, but stuffed with vegetables. And there's chicken and some sour vegetables with a little bit of sweet and sour sauce.
Oh, yes, I just tried to mess it up. It's the one with pak choi and stuff.
Wow, nice. It looks like something I can eat easily.
I like the sandwich type.
Oh, sure, it could be shkumelery.
Ah!
There are shkumerollies around here.
They are no longer available at Matsuya.
Oh, I see.
It was only available for a limited time.
I guess I'll have to serve it. Where does shkumerli come from? Georgia. Georgia. It's Georgian food. Hawaiian and Georgia.
Put them together. It's so good! So good! Kumansman! Yes!
That's nice. I wonder what else they have at Shkumerli's? What else does Georgia have? What else does Georgia have? Do they have sweets?
Drinks? Oh, sure.
I'm thinking of opening a Georgia-type store.
It's kind of new.
Who knows?
It's summer, isn't it? You burn a lot of energy, so garlic is really good for you. Shoku Meruri.
Oh, that's nice.
So I think it's fun.
That's nice. I'll definitely eat the food merry-go-round. That's nice. He said he'll definitely eat the food Merli.
I think it'll be fun.
Yay! I'm going to eat Meruri while sweating.
I think Georgia coffee would be good.
Ah! I've heard of Georgia. Georgia comes from Georgia.
There is a coffee maker called Georgia, isn't there?
Is there?
Yes, there is.
Wow!
Maybe that's where Georgia Coffee came from.
Wow! I see.
Then it's possible to serve coffee together.
Yes, that's possible.
Everyone drinks coffee with adults.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe it's decided. Thanks to all of you.
Thank you very much.
I'll talk to the adults about this and see if we can make it happen.
I don't know yet, but I will give my opinion.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
That's all I have to say.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
And now, I would like to continue with this project.
I'd like to continue with this project, and call it “A Delightful May for Married Couples!
Oh!
Yes, I would like to spend the rest of the time doing a May-ish project,
You all know the term “May illness,” don't you?
Yes, there is.
What is May illness?
It may be a world that has nothing to do with the mind.
April is the month when a new semester starts, or when you start a new job hunt, etc. You get really fired up, don't you?
You get really fired up, don't you? Then, in May, I was working hard toward the rainy season,
I feel a little down in the dumps.
I see. It's gloomy, isn't it?
That's right. I feel like I've been working too hard, and I'm a little tired. Yes, yes. I've been working too hard, and I'm a little tired.
Let's all blame May for that.
Like, “I'm getting May blues, so I'm not going to work too hard.
I guess that's the word people often use.
I see.
Am I right?
That's how it is.
You mean that you will have Golden Week, but you will be depressed afterwards?
Yes, that's right. After a long vacation, yes.
Ehhhh...
It is depressing, isn't it? This year's Golden Week was especially long, wasn't it? As I recall.
I think it was a combination of various consecutive holidays.
It was indeed very long.
Yes, it was. But, you know, it was not a jolly one. You know.
Ups and downs, I'm sure you don't have anything to do with it.
It doesn't matter what time of year it is. To be honest.
Certainly. No, it's not.
Tell that to everyone who is covered in reasons for this May illness.
It doesn't matter. Live in the moment.
LOL.
I feel like I've already helped someone who's suffering from May Sickness.
Really?
It's something to do with atmospheric pressure or something.
Not necessarily gloom.
You have to have a happy wine like Cocona.
Barometric pressure can take its toll on you.
What do you think about when you feel like that?
Take some of that.
Take a Chocola BB.
I'm good for barometric pressure too, to be honest.
Oh, I see.
So if you feel a little sleepy or heavy-headed today, I think you should take Chocola BB.
That's true, I often take Cocona.
That's the reason.
She said she takes it because it tastes good.
That's one reason.
I like the taste too. You like the taste? To be honest, I really like the taste of Chocola BB and Oronamin C. I also like the taste. Like the taste? To be honest, I really like the taste of Chocola BB and Oronamin C-type products.
Wait, are Chocola BB and Oronamin C the same? Oronamin C tastes good, but Chocola BB has a very unique taste.
I like it a lot. I also like Yunkel. What? You like Yunkel? I love Yunkel.
Yunkel seems to be a drink that everyone drinks as a soup. Then, I'm not so bad at all.
Can you afford it?
Just drink it with a whiff.
Wow.
That's amazing. Coconut pie is different.
It's different.
Just by drinking Yunkel.
I got praised just for taking Yunkel.
It's different. You are strong in energy drinks, aren't you?
I really like energy drinks.
Then, carbonated drinks, you know, the canned ones.
Like Monster.
Monster.
Do you drink those too? I drink a lot.
I can drink Monster, but if I drink it,
I stay awake all day. That's how strong it is.
Oh, I see. I have a lot of energy.
I feel fine for the whole day.
That's a problem, isn't it? I can't sleep when I want to.
When I was in the nap room with Yuno,
Yuno doesn't usually move so quickly.
That's true.
After drinking a little Monster, she suddenly started cleaning up.
Is it really that powerful?
I was like, “Do it here, too.
I thought it would be better not to let him drink Monster. I'm going to tell everyone to clean up.
I think Monster is a little high in caffeine. I think it's like Red Full or something.
I see. So Chocola BB is good for Cocona. Chocola BB is like Yunkel.
Yes, it is Yunkel, isn't it? I see. I think it's a little bit low. Then, let's all follow Dr. Cocona's advice,
When you are in a bit of pain, you can rely on energy drinks like that,
OK!
I'll get through the rest here.
That's for sure. With mind. Let's get over it.
Let's get over it.
It doesn't matter.It doesn't matter...5 shots don't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Because I got a quote.
Because there's no 5-shot.
That's a great quote. You're right.
Seriously, it doesn't matter.
When it falls, it falls. When it goes up, it goes up, right?
That's right. That's right.
That's what I'm talking about. Next time I have a problem, I'll ask for advice.
I'm sure you'll give me something to cheer me up.
You've been talking about guts all your life, haven't you?
That's really reassuring. Stay close to me.
Thank you.
That's settled.
Resolved.
Yes, it is. Everyone's problems are.
Resolved. I solved it on my own. On its own.
I'm sure those of you who are worried are sure that the results of your worries are all contained in the words you just said.
That's what it's all about, isn't it? That's what I think.
So let's continue the conversation. Yes, let's continue.
What would you like to talk about? I wonder if we can still plan a little more. Is it possible? Yes, I think so. What do you like?
There are a lot of themes here. I see.
What do you want to do, Ms. Cocona?
Ehhhh...
What do you like?
Hmmm...
Participation 5.
Participant 5?
So you want to try drawing?
Shall we?
Three.
Let's do a drawing of a memorable moment from the tour so far.
Ooooo...
I don't think I know much about Cocona's drawing skills.
No, it's fine.
It's good.
You sure? I'm a little nervous about the way you're saying that.
Okay? You know what?
You've been sketching the moment so far?
But isn't that what external forces are all about?
It's what the person sees and decides, isn't it?
He/she sees it and decides? The other person?
Because they like it or don't like it.
So you're saying you like them because they like you.
That's what they say.
Oh, yeah!
Ukyou yo today and once again, kudasame nazekei, thank you very much.
What I did on stage at the live performance, I don't want to spoil it for you
Yes, I'm afraid it might spoil what we did on stage at the concert, so I'll tell you about the episodes at the seller's house and other behind-the-scenes episodes.
You can't go inside, right?
Inside? During the concert?
Inside.
But it's okay, isn't it? If it's not a spoiler, I don't know.
If it's not a spoiler, it's OK.
Thank you for watching.
I got serious.
It's hard to draw, isn't it?
I'm good at drawing. I think I'm pretty good at it.
I've never seen you draw so many pictures.
I haven't had a chance to see your paintings.
That's great.
Okay, it's done.
I think I caught a glimpse of it. Around here.
I got a glimpse.
Okay, I'll make my announcement first.
The most memorable moment of the tour, here!
Dolan!
Why do you say that? What the hell is this?
This was the night of the Fukuoka show?
After the show, we all said let's go out for dinner since we were all there,
When the principal took us out to dinner,
When the principal took us out to eat, Cocona told us that there had been a rule for a long time that younger sisters were not allowed to go out to eat until late at night,
At that time, Cocona said to the manager, “Look, Cocona-san is going home,
When Cocona was told by the manager that she was going home, she said, “Oh, I'm so sad,
I thought it was cute that she said, “Oh, I'm so sad. I thought it was cute that he left saying, “Eh, I'm lonely.
Embarrassing.
Some of those instructions are in the picture.
Wait, is this me?
Cocona.
Is my foot flying off? That's me.
I used my feet to express my feeling of loneliness.
It's like, I want to stay here, but the manager is taking me away.
Oh, my feet want to be there, but I have to go.
Like, yeah, yeah, cocona won't go this way, I can't go.
Ah.
Indeed. Yeah, that was, you know, impressive. It's a metamorphic detachment.
That's for sure. Every time he says it, it's like he's finally done it.
By the way, who is this? That's me.
Is this Aya? Yes, this is me. This is me and this is the manager.
Oh, she was angry. She's angry and says she's leaving.
Aya-chan also looks like she wants me to leave.
Aya-chan, Aya-chan, Aya-chan. That's right. She's like, “Go home already.
She's saying, “I'll miss you.
Aya-chan is saying that too. She's saying “I miss you.
What? That's such a side of you too.
Sezuragi kogara-san, you also have a side of a lonely roof, don't you? Yes, I really wanted to talk to you, didn't I?
I'm sure you were having a great time with Aya, me, Emma, Riko, and Riko.
I knew it!
If you said you were leaving when we came in...
I don't want to leave.
Like, “Oh, no!
Can't I stay? Like that.
I'm 18 years old.
I don't think so.
I'm 19.
You were resisting so much, weren't you?
He said, “No, you can't do that. We're going home.
Isn't that crazy? I mean...
You should have reacted.
Like, “Cocona, you're an adult now.
She's an adult now, and she needs to do this.
“Please match, Cocona, she's 18 years old and an adult. Please match, Ms. Cocona, I'm 18 years old and I'm an adult.
They only call me an adult when it suits them.
“Okay, Ms. Cocona, you're only 18, so let's go home.
“She's 18, so let's go home” or “She's 18, so she can't go home.
I don't think it's good to say that only when it's not convenient.
I think it's a difficult age, really.
You're a rapper with a great mindset, aren't you?
When he complains, he's just saying that he's unhappy.
Not yet.
First of all, you're an adult, and you don't understand me.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah...
I'm sure it's a 1819 thing... but when I was younger, I used to rebel against him... calling him an adult, treating him like a child... and saying he's a child.
I don't know... does he ever rebel?
I'm afraid of him...
When they want to fight? He fights.
Scary, scary...
I have rebellious moments from time to time.
I still have those moments, even now. Even now, when I'm in charge, if I think this is unreasonable, or this is not right, I'm pretty aggressive.
But it's cool.
I want to be an adult like that. I'll say it like this.
You say it like this? I've never seen that before.
I've never seen it done. It's done behind the scenes.
We do it behind the scenes.
I'm doing it behind the scenes.
I see.
Then it's got to be a problem piece by Cocona.
Cocona's test, please. This way, please.
I have no idea. Don't you understand?
This is during a live performance. On stage? This one here, this one there.
Do you know what this is? I'm a little scared I recognized it. Shoes? Yes, yes.
I'm pretty sure they're not shoes, but these are feet, and these arrows are supporting them, so you can't tell they're shoes.
I don't know that they're shoes... because they're shoes... with a shoulder pattern... but they're different... because our shoes are shaped like this... for the tour.
What do they look like? Explain? They're not sneakers. This is the heel.
And here's the length of the shoe, the ankle part, the ankle part...
That's what these cream buns are made of.
It's a foot. From the foot. Is it swollen like this? Feet. They are swollen. I'm dancing.
This is from a certain song, and I think you can tell from the number of people watching,
I see. It's a song about the Olympics. It just fell out.I see. It's the song for the Olympics. It just slipped out.
Oh, you did? That's right. And the timing was right when it fell out.
I had to go to the top of the stairs, and I thought, “What am I going to do, pick up these shoes and carry them up the stairs.
I finished wearing them by the time of my rap part and did a cool rap. Thank God I made it in time. I made it in time.
These shoes look a little difficult to put on. How can I run in these shoes? How can you run in these shoes?
I'm sure they won't fit. They are so crammed in.
I was like, “I can't fit in these shoes. But we made it in time.
I'm so glad. I was Cinderella, wasn't I?
I tend to skip the shoes first.
Oh, but I'm sure I've seen it a few times.
Why is that?
I often skip them when I'm in the rear.
That's for sure.
What a thing to say. He must have a lot of momentum.
Do you have soft ankles?
My ankles are soft.
You have to kind of buzz around them a little bit to get them off, don't you?
I have nerves all the way down to my feet.
Everyone has nerves. They all have nerves when they're being moved.
I think they have feelings. In the feet.
I have feelings in my legs, and I think it's time to go.
I think it's time to come on. It's time for an emotional explosion.
I wonder. Maybe it's doubt?
I see.
I found a good one, though.
Thank you very much.
You are indeed a certified artist.
Really?
Yes, it is.
Yay!
Yay! I guess so.
Painter is a nice word.
Painter is like that, right? I guess you could say he has a unique sense of style.
I'm certified as unique.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, that's all for now, a pleasant and married May. Yes. So, that's it, a pleasant and conjugal May.
Yes, Ev-tune, in this seminar, happy lucky touch, happy turn touch.
I've never heard of it before, is that a fad?
Happy, what was it, Happy Turn?
Uh, Happy Turn ice cream?
Happy Ascreme!
That's what they say from the camera.
Oh, that's right.
I made a mistake.
I heard it for the first time. The arrangement was a little bit like Ammika's.
Like “Happy Lucky Dream.
It was a bit like that.
I made a mistake, though,
The 69th edition of the showroom of a couple with a special order is coming to an end in no time at all.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, I guess I should make an announcement here.
Yes, I think so.
I think we should do it.
This way?
It all happened so fast, didn't it? It went so fast.
Okay, then. Okay, yes.
I'm going to talk. Don't look at me and smile here.
Yebichu!
Summer Family Field Trip, or “Famie in Yamanaka” for short, will be held on August 17 and 18.
As was mentioned earlier in the Wu-Tang Village, of course you can look forward to the kitchen car,
Familian will be a hot and extremely enjoyable outdoor concert in full bloom in summer, with water effects,
It's a very popular event among the members, isn't it?
Yes, that's right. I love this event.
I hope everyone will be excited for the two days again this year.
And... Saitama Super Arena is coming!
Saitama Super Arena is decided!
So, on March 20th, we will have a big and simple event,
On the 20th of March, it's a big and simple announcement. And I'm calling it as it is.
I've been told many times. Surely. He pinched me open several times!
Isn't that what they did? We've decided to perform at Saitama Super Arena, which was our goal.
Okay! All right! All right! Yes! Yes! Yes!
All right! Suddenly Aiina's on your mind.
Okay! Okay!
Here's the thing... she's really into this stuff.
From now on!
I'm hoping to make the most exciting live show with you all.
I hope you will invite your friends and family and come to the show with us.
If you want to come and see us, please invite your friends and come to the show, and be prepared for March 20th!
We're waiting for you! We are waiting for you!
And on a personal note...
Could it be?
YAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAY! A birthday party will be held!
It's very simple, very simple...
It will be held on June 17 in Osaka, 18 in Nagoya, and 26 in Yokohama.
We are going to hold the birthday party on June 17 in Osaka, 18 in Nagoya, 26 in Yokohama, and we are going to broadcast it everyday on sns. If you have any friends who like idols or love music, please invite them to join us.
Now I'll show you the top 5 of the final ranking in the advertisement.
Okay, I'll let Cocona-san introduce them to you.
Okay, we'll start with number 5.
Fifth place, Natsumi.
Thank you very much.
Third place, Mr. Vartan.
2nd place, Mr. Nappo
Thank you very much.
Mr. Rikku, 1st place
Thank you very much!
Thank you for everything
And that brings us to the end of the 69th edition of Shrimp in the Shrimp Showroom.
We'll let you know about the next installment as soon as it's decided.
It was a lot of fun today. We had a lot of fun. It's been like this for a long time.
I think that Cocona-san is going to be a really reassuring adviser from now on.
I think she's going to be a really good adviser for us. No matter what I say, she will encourage me with her Cocona mind.
Leave it to me!
Leave it to me...
Leave it to me! Leave it to me!
Leave it to me!
I'll take care of it!
I don't want to trust you anymore!
What?
So cute!
I regret it now.
Regret? That's what I'm talking about.
How was your day, Cocona? Yes, it was good. You say you are a peaceful duo. But I don't think they are at all comfortable.
I thought so from the beginning. I wonder if this was named by a fan?
Only from Cocona? It's me. Maybe the year before last.
When I put “Yasuragi” on the website, a lot of fans said “Yasuragi, Yasuragi” and it became popular.
When I said, “We are Yasuragi,” did I mean the two Yasuragi people?
It's definitely different.
The fans are not so much “easygoing” as they are energetic. They are energetic.
So that gap between the two of us is also different.
In a way, they are energized and at ease.
That's right.
Forcedly, yes.
I've been forcing the connection.
I've connected them.
But I think it's good. I feel like I can feel the gap.
Indeed. We are a gap.
We are the gap.
Yes, we are. We were a gap duo.
Thank you very much.
So that's all for now.